Guide to the Office of University Special Events records, 1981-2011 RG0111
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Office of University Special Events records
1981-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Office of University Special Events
RG0111
52.5 Linear Feet
Collection includes shovels for building groundbreakings, medals, invitations, commencement guides, programs, 175th anniversary celebration of the University items, t-shirts, hats, posters.
Restrictions on Access
Series 13 is closed to research for 25 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Office of University Special Events.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Office of University Events is a division of the Office of the Vice President for Communications. The Office of University Events plays a role in a wide variety of events held on and off campus, including academic lectures, groundbreakings and grand openings, President's Medal presentations, convocations, and television and radio events in the Media and Public Affairs Building, just to name a few. The office is also an information resource for others on campus who are planning events and would like guidance and advice.
Michael Freedman, Vice President for Communications, also oversees the Office of University Relations and The George Washington University Printing and Graphics.
GW was recognized by Congress in 1996. A bill was introduced originally in January, but was read on February 7, 1996: "By Mr. Inouye: S. Con. Res. 41. A concurrent resolution expressing the sense of the Congress that The George Washington University is important to the Nation and urging that the importance of the University be recognized and celebrated through regular ceremonies; to the Committee on the Judiciary."
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection includes shovels for building groundbreakings, a framed drawing of the University ceremonial mace, medals, invitations, commencement guides, programs commemorative items, 175th anniversary celebration of the University items, a framed certificate, hard hats, t-shirts, sweat shirts, hats, posters, residence remodelling of the Shouse (Alumni) house, lecture series, and monumental celebration. They range in date from 1981 to 2011. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into nineteen series: Commemorative items and Publicity materials, Commencement videos, Special events memorabilia, Dorm groundbreaking, Clothing and apparel, Charter day posters, 175th anniversary catalog items, 175th anniversary items, Event posters, Posters, Posters and specifications, 175th anniversary celebration materials, 175th anniversary electronic time capsule, Sweat shirt, Memorabilia, 175th anniversary banners, Drawing of University mace,175th anniversary unused posters, and office files.
Commencement ceremonies -- Washington (D.C.); Events; Anniversaries; Lectures and lecturing; Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Washington (D.C.); George Washington University
- Commemorative items and publicity materials, 1991-1993; RG0111 Series 1; 2 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 3, Box 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series is a collection of medals, invitations, announcements, commencement guides, programs, commemorative items and logos. They range in date from 1991 to 1993. Some of events include Augustus tack, inaugural ball monumental celebration, and The George Washington University's 175th anniversary. Some of the commemorative items include: sunglasses, cups, paperweights, bottles of wine, etc.
  - Letter explaining medals, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Martin Luther King medals, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    General note
    4 copies in red boxes, old style without the neck ribbon
  - Distinguished Scholar Awards (GW Key Awards), undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    8 copies in black boxes, pre-1993 version
  - Distinguished Scholar Award paperweight, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    In white box, 1993 version
  - Mold for Martin Luther King lapel pins, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Paperweight with the invitation to the opening of the Virginia Campus, 09/25/1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Inagural Ball medals, 01/20/1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    6 medals
  - Invitations to Claire Bloom's performance of Sisters, Wives, and Daughters, 02/10/1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Announcements for 1993 commencement, 05/09/1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Announcements for 1993 National Law Center commencement, 05/30/1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Invitation to the presentation on Augustus Vincent Tack, 06/30/1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - MLK Convocation, 01/26/1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Invitations, programs, list of community service organizations.
  - Tickets and invitations to the GWU Inaugural Ball, 01/20/1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Invitations and programs for 1992 Fall Convocation, 09/11/1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - GWU certificates for outstanding academic achievement and distinguished scholar award, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Program for Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 05/08/1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Convocation for Vaclav Havel, President of the Czech Republic, 04/22/1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Monumental Celebration at Union Station, 05/08/1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Party for GW graduates, tickets and invitations
  - Commencements, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Winter (2/16/92) and May (5/10/92) commencement guides and tickets
  - Commencements, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Winter (2/14/93) and May (5/9/93) commencement guides, tickets, and banner information
  - Diane Schuur's performance, 10/14/1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Invitations and programs
  - Wine from Monumental Celebration, 05/08/1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    2 bottles
  - Champagne from Monumental Celebration, 05/08/1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Napkins from Monumental Celebration, 05/08/1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cup with pieces of old Lisner carpet from Diane Schuur's performance, 01/1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Rain ponchos, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    3, for use in case of rain at commencement
  - Binoculars from 1992 commencement, 5/10/1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Binoculars from 1993 commencement, 5/09/1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Handouts from the Monumental Celebrations, 5/08/1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Sunglasses from 1993 commencement, 5/09/1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Sunglasses from 1992 commencement, 5/10/1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Commencement videos, 1988-1991; RG0111 Series 2; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series is a collection of VHS video tapes of commencements. They range in date from 1988 to 1991.
  - School of Medicine and Health Sciences Commencement, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Spring semester
  - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences Commencement, 05/08/1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Tape 2
  - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences Commencement, 05/1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - School of Government and Business Administration, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Tape 1, three copies
  - School of Government and Business Administration, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Tape 2, three copies
  - School of Government and Business Administration Commencement, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Part 2
  - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences [1/2], 05/1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences Commencement [2/2], 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - School of Education and Human Development Commencement, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Winter commencement, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - School of Government and Business Administration Commencement, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Tape 1
  - School of Government and Business Administration Commencement, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - School of Government and Business Administration Commencement, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Eliott School of International Affairs Commencement, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Spring
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 05/12/1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Winter Commencement, 02/17/1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Two copies
  - School of Engineering and Applied Science Commencement, 05/12/1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Special events memorabilia, 1993-2011; RG0111 Series 3; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series is a collection of sunglasses, hats, buttons, invitations, programs, tickets, and other memorabilia from special events. They range in date from 1993 to 2011.
  - Sunglasses, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Printed on the sides: The George Washington University, Washington, D.C.
  - Orange hat, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Blue letters on front: The George Washington University, Washington, D.C.
  - Blue hat, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Yellow letters on front: The George Washington University, Washington, D.C.; red letters: 1993 Colonial Convocation
  - Black and gold pen with case, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Etched in gold letters: The George Washington University, Washington, D.C., School of Medicine and Health Sciences Commencement 1994
  - George Washington pin with case, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Shot glass, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Inscription: The George Washington University, Washington, D.C., Monumental Celebration 1994
  - Yellow pin, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Inscription: Countdown to Commencement; The George Washington University DC Monumental Celebration at Union Square 5/7/94
  - Orange pin, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Purple pin, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Yellow pin, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Inscription: Colonial Convocation; The George Washington University DC Lisner Auditorium 12:45 p.m. Monday August 30, 1993
  - 2 yellow paper made binoculars (folded up), undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Inscription: The George Washington University DC. 3.0 power, made in China
  - White cloth lunch bag, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    On front, a green design of a person's shadow with arms in the air. Within the design "The George Washington University DC" Underneath the design it states in green "The Green University" and "Made from 100% post-consumer recycled plastic soda bottles."
  - Convocation program honoring Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., 01/24/1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Eight Monumental Celebration Invitations at Union Station, 05/07/1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Invitation to a dinner at President Trachtenberg's house in honor of the Ambassador of Saudi Arabia, 10/26/1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Invitation to President Trachtenberg's house in honor of Dr. Chong-Kuk Sohn, 01/17/1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2 metal bookmarks in gold that formed part of the Canadian Brass/President's Night Performance programs, 01/17/1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Designed in rectangular shape with a trumpet on top, below is stated: The George Washington University DC Lisner Auditorium Concert Line 994-1500
  - Invitation for the dedication of the John A. Wilson Park, 10/28/1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Invitation for the George Washington University Ambassador's Lecture Series, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 5 Canadian Brass/President's Night Performance programs, 10/27/1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 2 Invitations to the Canadian Brass/President's Night Performance, 10/27/1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 5 Tickets to the Canadian Brass/President's Night Performance, 10/27/1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 9 Sticker sheets (return address stickers) of the 175th Anniversary of George Washington University, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 7 Cardboard pamphlet invitations plus 1 regular cardboard invitation to the Convocation in honor of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., 01/24/1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Invitation to Dinner honoring Gary Wills, 02/09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Invitation to the Marcus Cunliffe Memorial Lecture, 02/09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Small booklet: "A Guide to Commencement", 05/06/1994 --05/08/1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 3 Tickets to a Monumental Celebration, 05/07/1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 2 Doctoral Hooding Ceremony tickets, 05/07/1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Seating arrangement and school color banner charts for Graduation on the ellipse, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Six in all
  - Commencement reminder for Monumental Celebration tickets, 04/1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Holiday Card that states "Season's Greetings" from President Trachtenberg, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Colonial Convocation pamphlet, 08/30/1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Program for "GW Celebrates Vincent Gray", 13 January 2011; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Commemorative medal for GW Inaugural Ball for President Barack Obama and Vice President Joe Biden, 20 January 2009; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Dorm groundbreaking, 1995; RG0111 Series 4; 1 Linear feet
  This series is a collection of a hard hat, a golden shovel, and a t-shirt from the groundbreaking for a dormitory (New Hall). They are from October 26, 1995.
  - Hard hat, 10/26/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    For the groundbreaking of the new dorm (New Hall)
  - Gold shovel, 10/26/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - T-shirt, 10/26/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Clothing and apparel, 1989-1995; RG0111 Series 5; 3 Linear feet
  This series is a collection of t-shirts, hats, and sweat-shirts. They range in date from 1989 to 1995. They were made for several of The George Washington University events including Martha's Marathon, Welcome week, commencement, and other events.
  - Martha's Marathon, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Martha's Marathon goes to Moscow, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Martha's Marathon, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Martha's Marathon, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gee whiz: gwis information system, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Martha's Marathon, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GW Basketball: It's Like ... Workin' out!, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Approved for NCAA Competition: Colonials why you came to the Game, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Where Else??, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - GWizard: GW's Information System, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Senior Week, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    My Last Free T-Shirt: Countdown to Reality
  - Inaugural Media Center, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Martha's Marathon, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Martha's Marathon, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ski MC: Ski patrol, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Student Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Welcome Week, 08/1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Welcome Week, 08/1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Best Neighbors are Diplomatic, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 70's Week, 01/1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Tie dyed
  - Welcome Week, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 70's Week, 01/1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Residence Hall Association Sweatshirt, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Hat: Commencement 1995, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Hat: Commencement 1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Hat: Commencement 1993, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Gold
  - Hat: Commencement 1993, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    White
  - GW Colonials, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The George Washington Universtiy Colonials, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Colonial Convocation, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Charter day posters, 1996; RG0111 Series 6; 1 Linear feet (Flat box 1)
  This material is a collection of two charter day posters with two pairs 3-D glasses. They are from February 9, 1996. The glasses are used on the posters.
  - 175th Anniversary Charter Day Celebration poster, 02/09/1996 (Flat box 1, Folder 1)
    2 posters in 3-D
  - 3-D glasses, undated (Flat box 1, Folder 2)
    2 pairs
- 175th anniversary catalog items, 1996; RG0111 Series 7; 4 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series is a collection of 175th anniversary catalog items, including t-shirts, pins, paperweight, coasters, aprons, hats, ties, calendar, strength to strength book, etc. They are from 1996.
  - Sweatshirts, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Various designs and colors. 4 sweatshirts
  - Tie, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Scarf, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - T-shirts, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    2 shirts
  - Rugby Shirt, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Catalog of items, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Golf Balls, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    3 items
  - Coffee Mug, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Note Pad, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Pins, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Pencils, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    2 items
  - Coaster, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Magnet, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Glass set, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    4 items
  - Paper Weight, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Rugby Shirts, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Hat, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Tote bag, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Apron, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Watches, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mini Flag, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Pepsi Can, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Calendar, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    2 Calendars
  - Book: From Strength to Strength, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 175th anniversary items, 1996; RG0111 Series 8; 1.5 Linear feet
  The materials in this series are contained in one box. It is a collection of The George Washington University's 175th anniversary items including Pepsi cans and papers by Schwoerer, Millar, Greir, Danielson, and Miller. It also includes new dorm paperweight and Charter Day commemorative Pepsi cans. They are from 1996.
  - 1 six pack of Pepsi: 175th commemorative cans, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1 six pack of Pepsi: Charter Day commemorative cans, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ground breaking for new residence hall: paperweight, 10/26/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The GW University 175th Anniversary Papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Lois G. Schwoerer, "Images of Queen Mary II"
  - The GW University 175th Anniversary Papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    James R. Millar, "From Utopian Socialism to Utopian Capitalism: The Failure of Revolution And Reform In Post-Soviet Russia"
  - The GW University 175th Anniversary Papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    David Alan Grier, "Statistics and the Introduction of Digital Computers"
  - The GW University 175th Anniversary Papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Eric N. Danielson, "The Historic Roots of the Recent Balkan Conflict"
  - The GW University 175th Anniversary Papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Houston Miller, Deborah Hill, "Lost In the Ozone: A Layman's Guide to Hot Topics In Atmospheric Chemistry"
- Event posters, 1996; RG0111 Series 9; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series is a collection of posters depicting the following: homecoming, Charter day weekend, basketball, and a Martin Luther King Jr. Convocation. They are from 1996.
  - Charter day celebration homecoming weekend, 02/05/1996 --02/12/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Charter day celebration homecoming weekend, 02/05/1996 --02/12/1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Charter day celebration homecoming weekend, 02/05/1996 --02/12/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Men's basketball "Play It Up", 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Women's basketball, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Women's basketball, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Dream in Action: a Convocation in Honor of the Life and Spirit of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Posters, 1995-1996; RG0111 Series 10; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  The materials in this series are a collection of posters and 3D-glasses. They range in date from 1995 to 1996. The posters depict the following: Charter Day, opening convocation, Martin Luther King Jr. Convocation, ambassador lecture series, monumental celebration (graduation), The George Washington University's 175th anniversary, and more.
  - 3D Poster with Glasses: 175th anniversary charter day celebration, 02/09/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    3 copies
  - Charter Day Celebration and Homecoming Weekend, 02/05/1996 --02/12/1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - illuminate: Opening convocation, 08/28/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    4 copies
  - From Strength to Strength book cover, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Dream in Action, MLK, 01/23/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Monumental Celebration, 05/18/1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Knowledge is in every country the surest basis of public happiness, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    5 copies
  - Ambassadors Lecture Series, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Dated Fall. 2 copies
  - Ambassadors Lecture Series, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Dated Spring. 2 copies
  - The Fine Art of Campus Life, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Posters and specifications, 1991-1995; RG0111 Series 11; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 1, Box 2)
  This series is a collection of specifications for the residence remodelling of Shouse (Alumni) House, and posters for ten campus events. They range in date from 1991 to 1995.
  - Specifications for Remodeling of residence for Mrs. Jouette Shouse (Alumni House), undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Mrs. Joutte Shouse, undated; Series 11 (Box 3)
    General
    There is also some data about the Lawson-Whitney Houses at 1916 and 1918 F Street, NW.
  - Women's History Month, 03/1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    2 copies
  - Monumental Celebration, 05/07/1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Student financial assistance, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Dream in Action, 01/18/1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Dream in Action, 01/1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Dream in Action, 01/15/1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Opening Convocation, 09/06/1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - World in Motion, 04/04/1994 --04/10/1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - AIDS Awareness Week, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Thrillo: Welcome Week, 08/26/1993 --09/06/1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Opening Convocation, 08/29/1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ambassadors Lecture Series, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ambassadors Lecture Series, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ambassadors Lecture Series, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 175th anniversary celebration materials, 1996; RG0111 Series 12; 28 Linear feet (Box 19, Box 4, Box 1, Box 3, Box 2)
  This series is a collection of The George Washington University's 175th anniversary celebration materials including: commemorative publications, proposals, proclamations, hats, shirts, pens, sunglasses, flags, panorama photographs of commencement, special events programs, graphics, videos, correspondence, and more. They are from 1996.
  GW was recognized by Congress in 1996. A bill was introduced originally in January, but was read on February 7, 1996: "By Mr. Inouye: S. Con. Res. 41. A concurrent resolution expressing the sense of the Congress that The George Washington University is important to the Nation and urging that the importance of the University be recognized and celebrated through regular ceremonies; to the Committee on the Judiciary."
  - Lost In The Ozone, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - brochure - Wellesley College, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Book of Photographs of Washington D.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Framed collection - Stamps of George Washington (The Man), undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Book - The History of the University at Albany, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Flag - United States Flag, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proclamation, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Commemorative calendars, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    8 calendars
  - GW Opening Convocation Hat, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - GW Opening Convocation T Shirts, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - GW Opening Convocation Posters, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    5 posters
  - Opening Convocation Pamphlets, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    27 Pamphlets
  - Folder of Caller Anniversary Sheets, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Flags, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    4 flags
  - Letter From Washington State, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Letter From Washington County Alabama, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Letter From Washington County Idaho, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Letter From Washington County Florida, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Letter From Washington County Indiana, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Letter From Washington County Maryland, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Letter From Washington County Vermont, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Letter From Central Washington University, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)